<rss version="2.0"><channel><ttl>60</ttl><title>Science</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/section/science</link><description>Science news from The New York Times. Get the latest developments about space, the environment, animal behavior, the brain, genetics, archeology and robots along with the weekly Science Times.</description><copyright>Copyright 2016 The New York Times Company</copyright><language>en-us</language><item><title>Elon Musk Says SpaceX Rocket Launches Might Resume Next Month</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/05/science/elon-musk-spacex-rocket-launches.html</link><description>The chief executive of SpaceX outlined some details of what caused a rocket explosion in September.</description><author>By KENNETH CHANG</author><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 17:23:32 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>How Is Your Family Coping With Delhi&#8217;s Air Pollution?</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/05/world/asia/how-is-your-family-coping-with-delhis-air-pollution.html</link><description>The Times would like to hear from parents whose children are staying home from school to avoid exposure to dangerous levels of air pollution.</description><author>By THE NEW YORK TIMES</author><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 16:51:05 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>If a &#8216;Big Whack&#8217; Made the Moon, Did it Also Knock the Earth on Its Side?</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/08/science/moon-formation.html</link><description>A new study suggests that it did. It also explains that the collision can explain the formation of the moon without a second event.</description><author>By KENNETH CHANG</author><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 16:14:09 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Delhi Closes Over 1,800 Schools in Response to Dangerous Smog</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/05/world/asia/delhi-closes-over-1800-schools-in-response-to-dangerous-smog.html</link><description>The closings, part of an effort to shield children in India&#8217;s capital from air pollution, affect more than a million students.</description><author>By SUHASINI RAJ and ELLEN BARRY</author><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 13:43:59 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>A Slow Ride Toward the Future of Public Transportation</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/08/science/finland-public-transportation-driverless-bus.html</link><description>A self-driving bus being tested in Finland holds promise for reducing cities&#8217; dependence on cars.</description><author>By HENRY FOUNTAIN</author><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 10:36:56 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Whales Can Really Rock With Their Mellow Songs</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/05/science/whale-songs-vibration.html</link><description>A new study suggests that the vibrations from humpback whales have been overlooked and misunderstood. Underwater, they travel a long way.</description><author>By NICHOLAS ST. FLEUR</author><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 06:00:22 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Young Adolescents as Likely to Die From Suicide as From Traffic Accidents</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/04/health/suicide-adolescents-traffic-deaths.html</link><description>There are concerns that the pervasiveness and pressures of social media are contributing factors to a rising suicide rate for children ages 10 to 14.</description><author>By SABRINA TAVERNISE</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 16:54:04 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>When It Comes to Success, Age Really Is Just a Number</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/04/science/stem-careers-success-achievement.html</link><description>A new study points to a combination of personality, persistence and luck as leading to success, and scientists say that those same forces are at play at all levels of a discipline.</description><author>By BENEDICT CAREY</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 14:38:28 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>What Lady Gaga&#8217;s &#8216;Bad Romance&#8217; and Other Earworm Songs Have in Common</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/04/science/earworms-lady-gaga-bad-romance.html</link><description>In the largest ever study of songs that play on repeat in your head, researchers found earworms had unusual intervals along with fast melodies.</description><author>By JOANNA KLEIN</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 13:12:02 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Ebola Evolved Into Deadlier Enemy During the African Epidemic</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/04/science/ebola-evolution-african-epidemic.html</link><description>A mutated version of the virus was more effective at entering human cells, scientists report. The finding may help explain the vast scope of the last outbreak.</description><author>By CARL ZIMMER</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 12:01:47 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>