<rss version="2.0"><channel><ttl>60</ttl><title>Jobs</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/section/jobs</link><description>Job postings, plus insight and analysis from Times reporters and business leaders.</description><copyright>Copyright 2016 The New York Times Company</copyright><language>en-us</language><item><title>Preventing Factory Explosions by (Safely) Blowing Stuff Up</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/06/jobs/preventing-factory-explosions-by-safely-blowing-stuff-up.html</link><description>Jenny Chao, who tinkered in the garage as a child, is a mechanical engineer specializing in industrial explosions for a commercial property insurance company.</description><author>As told to PATRICIA R. OLSEN</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 11:42:04 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Want Co-Workers to Vote Your Way? Then Stop Pestering Them</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/06/jobs/want-co-workers-to-vote-your-way-then-stop-pestering-them.html</link><description>Studies have shown that people tend to consider unsolicited advice as a threat to their free will, and they will often protest by doing the opposite.</description><author>By GAVAN FITZSIMONS</author><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 07:00:28 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Deirdre Quinn: If a Meeting Starts at 9, Be There at 8</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/06/business/deirdre-quinn-if-a-meeting-starts-at-9-be-there-at-8.html</link><description>Ms. Quinn, chief of the women&#8217;s fashion site Lafayette 148 New York, says her pet peeve is lateness. When a meeting starts, she says, she closes the door.</description><author>By ADAM BRYANT</author><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2016 07:00:28 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>When It Comes to Success, Age Really Is Just a Number</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/04/science/stem-careers-success-achievement.html</link><description>A new study points to a combination of personality, persistence and luck as leading to success, and scientists say that those same forces are at play at all levels of a discipline.</description><author>By BENEDICT CAREY</author><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2016 14:38:28 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Bossy vs. Buddy: Two Leadership Styles, Each With Its Place</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/10/30/jobs/bossy-vs-buddy-two-leadership-styles-each-with-its-place.html</link><description>Some managers lead by dominating employees; others try to win them over. But the most effective leaders deploy the style best suited to the situation.</description><author>By PHYLLIS KORKKI</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 17:16:49 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Antique Teddy Bears and an Artist&#8217;s Trash: An &#8216;Art Dork&#8217; in Her Element</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/10/30/jobs/antique-teddy-bears-and-an-artists-trash-an-art-dork-in-her-element.html</link><description>Emily Weiss earned an art degree, but instead of becoming a starving artist, she got an insurance broker&#8217;s license and assesses works by major art world figures.</description><author>As told to PATRICIA R. OLSEN</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 11:21:31 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>We&#8217;re hiring three journalists to help shape opinion coverage at The New York Times</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2016/jobs/nyt-job-opinion-editors.html</link><description>In an editor role we're looking for a person who defines editing broadly, from written columns to interactive stories and reader engagement. We also seek two visual journalists to join the team.</description><author /><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 12:44:45 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Groped at a Party by a Colleague. Then You Become His Boss.</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/10/30/jobs/groped-at-a-party-by-a-colleague-then-you-become-his-boss.html</link><description>A woman did not report a harrowing incident involving a male colleague at a company holiday party. Then, a twist: That colleague became her subordinate.</description><author>By ROB WALKER</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 07:30:04 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Austin McChord of Datto: It&#8217;s Not Awesome Till It&#8217;s Awesome</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/10/30/business/austin-mcchord-of-datto-its-not-awesome-till-its-awesome.html</link><description>Austin McChord, C.E.O. of the data protection company Datto, says he resists the trend of automatically handing out praise and instead saves it for exceptional achievements.</description><author>By ADAM BRYANT</author><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2016 07:00:04 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>The New York Times is looking for a Deputy Video Editor</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2016/jobs/nyt-video-deputy-editor.html</link><description>We&#8217;re hiring the best talent to shape our on the ground and original reporting, experiment with new forms of video, and launch a new slate of shows and series.</description><author /><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 12:05:49 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>