<rss version="2.0"><channel><ttl>60</ttl><title>U.S.</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/section/us</link><description /><copyright>Copyright 2016 The New York Times Company</copyright><language>en-us</language><item><title>Why a Pot Farmer Opposes Legal Marijuana</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/video/us/politics/100000004726631/why-a-pot-farmer-opposes-legal-marijuana.html</link><description>A ballot initiative on Tuesday may be a turning point for marijuana growers in California. Visit a pot farm where the owner is against legalization for recreational use.</description><author>By HILARY SWIFT, NIKO KOPPEL and SAMANTHA QUICK</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 05:00:49 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>The Biggest Turning Points in a Polarizing Campaign</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/06/us/politics/trump-clinton-turning-points.html</link><description>The race between Donald J. Trump and Hillary Clinton has been one of the most contentious in modern American history. Here&#8217;s a look at how we covered major developments.</description><author>By LIAM STACK</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 05:00:31 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Presidential Election: Clinton Tries to Run Up a Lead as Trump Seeks a Breakthrough</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/06/us/politics/presidential-election.html</link><description>Donald J. Trump heads to the blue state of Minnesota in hopes of assembling an Electoral College win. Hillary Clinton&#8217;s top surrogate, President Obama, heads to Florida in a final push for early votes.</description><author>By ALEXANDER BURNS</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 05:00:06 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>South Carolina Man May Be Linked to 7 Killings, Authorities Say</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/06/us/south-carolina-man-linked-to-multiple-killings.html</link><description>A man charged in the kidnapping of a woman found alive confessed to the unsolved killings of four people in 2003, and may be linked to a total of seven deaths, the authorities said.</description><author>By CHRISTOPHER MELE</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 00:39:45 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Undocumented Migrants, Free Now to Visit Mexico, Face Iffy Future</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/06/world/americas/mexico-immigrants.html</link><description>Thousands of undocumented immigrants have used travel permission under a 2012 program to visit the countries they left as children. The program could be canceled.</description><author>By KIRK SEMPLE</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 23:02:44 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Naturalization: Becoming an American</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/video/us/100000004750106/naturalization-becoming-an-american.html</link><description>Carmen Joan Edwards spent 15 years trying to change her status from illegal immigrant to naturalized citizen. She is now eligible to vote on Election Day.</description><author>By NEETI UPADHYE</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 23:01:55 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Scenes From the Trump Rally in Reno</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/slideshow/2016/11/05/us/scenes-from-the-trump-rally-in-reno.html</link><description>Donald J. Trump was abruptly rushed offstage by security on Saturday night at the Reno-Sparks Convention Center.</description><author /><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 22:24:45 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>On the Trail: Saturday, Nov. 5</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/slideshow/2016/11/05/us/elections/on-the-trail-saturday-nov-5.html</link><description>Donald J. Trump and Hillary Clinton held rallies in North Carolina and Florida.</description><author /><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:31:51 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump-Clinton? Charter Schools Are the Big Issue on Massachusetts&#8217; Ballot</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/06/us/charter-schools-massachusetts-ballot.html</link><description>Question 2, if approved, would allow the state to expand charter schools. A pitched battle over the measure reflects the passions that the debate has aroused nationwide.</description><author>By KATHARINE Q. SEELYE and JESS BIDGOOD</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:28:14 -0500</pubDate></item><item><title>Donald Trump Rushed Offstage by Secret Service Agents</title><link>http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/06/us/politics/donald-trump-rally.html</link><description>A man thought to have a gun was apprehended on Saturday night at a Trump rally in Reno, Nev., but no weapon was found, the Secret Service said, and the man was released.</description><author>By ASHLEY PARKER and MICHAEL BARBARO</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:24:53 -0500</pubDate></item></channel></rss>